It has started!
Yeah!
It's a new world.
It's like a place where you can do a
lot of things.
It's like that.
It's like a center.
What are we going to do?
This week is...
Last time, we did the Kanameiyo test at
Marumaru.
Do you remember that?
Of course.
There's no way we can forget.
We were in front of the test.
We were like...
We were spread out.
We were like a big family.
It was like a big family.
Hiori said,
when we were trying to get started,
what was it?
She said,
let's do it!
That was the most fun.
I thought you were the one who set it
up.
You're cute.
You were cute.
So,
what are we going to do this time?
Last time,
we did the adult women,
Oharu-chan,
who was chosen as a new member.
We're going to do that.
Thank you for watching!
You look sexy in this photo.
Are you kidding me?
You look like a girl.
I'm not a girl.
You look like a man.
You know,
recently,
you look like a sexy girl in Lion Girl.
You look like a girl in Lion Girl.
I love this.
You look like a girl.
Please subscribe to this channel!
We met like this in Japan.
We met like this.
We met like this a lot.
I see this a lot.
I know what you mean.
Please subscribe to this channel!
I don't know.
Whose is this?
It's Shizu's.
I don't know if I can tell.
TikTok or EnVy.
I know this.
I know this, but today...
I know.
I'm talking about myself.
No, I'm talking about sexy.
That's good.
I'm talking about cute.
No, no, no.
I'm talking about sexy.
We're both over 20 years old.
Let's move on.
You're all relaxed, aren't you?
We're relaxed.
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe to this channel!
We've been together for 6 years.
I've been putting on lipsticks
recently.
I remember what I was doing with my
lipstick on.
I'm scared of being on camera.
Who's confident?
No one!
But it says, I'll do my best.
Oh my!
Aoharu has a lot of affection for
Julia.
I think Julia thinks a lot about
Aoharu.
So I think she's watching a lot of
I used a lot of words.
I'm not confident.
I'm the MC today.
I'll ask Aki to explain the rules.
I'll explain the rules.
This time, we'll have a quiz about
Aoharu.
Aoharu has a lot of affection for
Julia.
We are going to answer the questions
that you have asked us.
It seems that it is easy to answer if
you understand Aoharu.
Let's do our best!
We will do our best!
1 point per person.
Oh, 1 point per person?
Wow.
1 point per person.
For those who got the highest score in
the total,
there's a punishment.
That's it!
Last time, it was a punishment game
where you had to be a bear.
What are we going to be this time?
A Jiju-guruma!
That's a bit difficult.
Let's do our best!
Let's go!
This program is a program where 6
people who are active to do something
new,
challenge themselves and raise the
barometer of their daily lives.
The first question!
What is Koharu's favorite food on the
super-special Kowaski website?
Corn potage!
What is the other one?
This is the profile from the beginning
of the tournament.
It hasn't changed.
I can see the difference.
It's always chubby.
It was chubby for a while.
You can see the difference if you look
at it.
Do you like it?
Yes, I do.
Do you eat it often?
It's not similar to the one I have.
It's different.
It's different from the one I have.
It's like...
What?
I'm sorry.
Please watch again.
When did I eat this?
I haven't eaten this recently.
A while ago.
What?
It's rare.
I've been eating this for a long time.
A while ago.
Thank you for watching. Please
subscribe to my channel.
I don't know what you're talking about.
This is it.
What?
I've been saying this.
But I can't remember what I said.
I know what you're talking about.
I've been saying this on the stage.
Oh, that's not it.
We only have 6 seconds left.
I don't know.
Let's see the answers!
Chocobat.
Ramen.
Chocobo.
You said it.
You said it at the live.
I couldn't hear it.
It was a moment.
Let's see the answer!
What is your favorite food in the
spring? Corn potage, Tantanmen, and what
is the last one?
The last one is...
Fruit!
Did you get it?
I don't get it at all.
But it's written on the homepage of the
organization.
I've never heard of it.
Do you have it?
No.
I've never heard of it.
I've never seen you eat it.
What is your favorite fruit?
I like peach.
I've never seen it.
I see.
It's difficult.
It's written on the homepage of the
organization.
Let's move on to the second question.
What was the most delicious thing that
you ate recently?
I think I've said this before.
I don't know.
Recently?
How many people?
How many?
Recently?
Recently is in this month?
About that.
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe to our channel!
There are some.
Is it this?
I ate it 3 times.
Then, it's not me.
Did you get it?
Let's open it!
Chocolate. Cup noodles.
Cherry blossom donut.
This is it.
Valentine's chocolate.
Yes, yes.
It's good.
It's like you're doing it for yourself.
I see.
Then, let's see the correct answer.
Next, Banzai!
What is the most delicious food you ate
recently?
The most delicious food I ate recently
is...
Shin Ramen's Kimchi flavor!
I wonder if everyone can tell.
I really like Shin Ramen.
I found a mild spicy Shin Ramen Kimchi
flavor.
It was a moderate spicy flavor and it
was very delicious.
It was the best to eat with rice.
Amazing!
You got it right!
We talked about it.
I thought it was a new name, but it was
a wide range.
That's right.
You are smart.
You said it was a plant, so I thought
it was a cherry blossom donut.
I thought it was a cherry blossom
donut.
It was written on the block.
It was written that it was delicious.
We have only eaten it once.
This is the first time I have eaten
Shin Ramen and Kimchi.
It's very delicious.
It's a little difficult.
There are many things to eat.
Can we go?
Please subscribe to this channel.
Let's move on to the next question.
What did you have for breakfast in the
spring?
I haven't told you the answer.
I haven't told you the story.
I'm just saying.
You'll know if I tell you.
But I eat a lot.
It's hard.
Ramen? From morning?
I can only think of ramen.
I think it's that kind of ramen.
I've definitely eaten it.
I've definitely talked to Hiyori about
it.
You can eat this in the morning.
But there are quite a lot of people who
say,
Did you eat it in the morning?
I'm the type of person who can eat
that.
So it's a lot.
I think so.
I've never eaten that kind of thing.
I think I can eat it.
It's hard.
It's over.
Everyone, it's over.
What?
Why do you look so handsome?
Curry.
One more time.
Why do you look so handsome?
I'm handsome.
What?
I'm asking you the right answer.
It's so funny.
It's too natural.
I have to say it because it's a
question.
One more time.
Pasta.
Love.
Curry.
I thought of curry, too.
I ate curry for breakfast before.
I can't eat it at all.
I can't eat it.
My bangs are messy.
The answer is...
What is your breakfast today?
My breakfast today is...
Pasta!
I ate a creamy bolognese every day.
I love it.
You did it!
Please subscribe to this channel!
I'm glad you like it.
It was a good experience.
I thought you ate pasta.
I ate it after warming it up.
It's good.
I got a good impression.
Everyone got 1 point.
What did you eat?
Thank you for watching.
I ate egg and salad.
What did you eat for breakfast?
I ate Anpanman.
Do you know that?
I like grapes the most.
Yes, yes.
Thank you for watching.
I want to eat the egg.
I want to eat the rice with soybean
flour.
I want to eat that.
I want to eat the rice with soybean
flour.
Let's move on to the next question.
What was the first thing Oharu tried
recently?
I wrote this on my blog.
What?
My manager told me to try this.
I'm sure I'm right.
I wrote it on my blog.
I did it yesterday.
I forgot where I was.
I think I will be addicted to it if I
do it once.
Really?
Maybe not.
I think it's not.
5 seconds ago.
OK, everyone.
Ready? Open!
I tried to play a song of Tochi-chan on
the guitar.
IZTV.
You did it.
No, I didn't.
I played the guitar on the guitar.
I see.
OK, let's start the VTR.
What is the first thing you tried
recently?
The first thing I tried recently is
Uber Eats.
Wait!
No way!
I thought you would say the same thing.
I thought so.
I thought you would say, I tried it.
What did you think?
No way!
But it's the same.
Really?
I tried Uber Eats for the first time.
What did you order?
Chicken.
Oh, you ordered chicken. I thought you
would say curry.
Curry.
What?
I thought you would say curry.
Oh, I like curry.
It's delicious.
I thought you would say the same thing.
I thought so.
I played the guitar in ICTV.
I saw you playing the guitar.
Let's move on to the next question.
What was your dream when you were a
child?
I'm sure I said this.
Dream?
I knew it.
But I think that's probably right.
What?
I'm sure I'm saying it.
I think it's a scene from the past.
What?
Let's say it together.
Juri is so tired.
Konyuu-san.
Konya-san.
What?
I thought it was written as cat.
Cat?
It's Konya.
Julia's answer is almost ramen.
Ramen.
I'm not kidding.
It's almost ramen.
Then, let's start the world cultural
exchange!
What is your future dream when you were
a child?
I think some people have already told
you this, but I want to be a bookstore
clerk.
I want to be a bookstore clerk and
publish books and carry books.
We got the same score!
Wow!
Kanamin and...
Hitoka?
Yurika!
Yurika and Yano got the same score!
We got the same score!
Wow!
The next is...
Okay! Let's go to the next one!
What does Oharu want to make next?
I haven't told you yet.
I want to make food.
I know what you want to make.
Really?
Do you know what I want to make?
That's it! Oharu!
I'm not sure.
I don't know anything about ramen.
Do you like it?
I like it.
I hope you know what I like.
I like pretty much everything.
Do you eat it often?
I do.
I eat it often at Chinese restaurants.
Cheese Choco
No way!
Chinese restaurant?
Ramen?
Let's open your answers!
Mapo Tofu
Sesame dumpling
Tofu
Gyoza
Gyoza!
I thought it was shrimp and chili.
How do you eat shrimp and chili?
From the beginning
From the soup
I want to try it.
It's hard.
Gyoza is...
I'm going to make it.
What do you mean?
Yes!
Please watch the next video!
What does Koharu want to make next?
The answer is...
Mabo Tofu!
It's Mabo Tofu!
I thought normal Mabo Tofu would be
good,
but I like spicy food,
so I want to make a Mabo Tofu that
looks like Shisen.
Amazing!
Correct!
Why did you get angry?
I don't know.
I think I can make fried rice.
I thought I would make it if I made it
for the first time.
I don't know.
I want to make Mabo Tofu.
I want to make something like Shisen
style.
So, you are the leader.
Good luck everyone!
Next!
What do you feel you've grown up a
little?
In what way?
In your private life.
Private life?
Like cooking?
Something like that.
I can think like that.
What? Think?
Let's open it!
Be careful of the food.
I have to make a meal.
You can decide what to eat right away.
This is a person.
Thank you for your viewing.
Well then,
Let's do it together.
Let's watch the video!
What do you feel you've grown as
yourself?
Yes, bye-bye!
What?
Oh, I see.
Yes!
Yes, I think I've grown as myself.
I've started to think that I should
cook myself once a week, twice a week,
or three times a week.
I think I've grown as myself.
Yes!
Wait, wait, wait.
I think I've grown as myself.
I'm right, right?
I think you're right.
But if you're not, you have to clean
up.
I have to be careful about my diet.
Why do you have to be careful about
your diet?
That's a big deal.
What?
What should I do? Can I decide?
That's a big deal.
Wait, wait.
I think you have to be careful about
your diet.
Can I decide?
Yes.
I'll do it!
Yes!
I'm glad.
Thank you.
Julia's answer is awesome.
She's like a mom who helps her kids.
A mom who helps her kids.
She's writing down everything that
seems to be right.
A mom who helps her kids.
You didn't have a fire in your stomach.
No.
I'm glad.
Hitoka and I are in the same group.
Please do your best!
Next question!
Which part of Julia do you like the
most?
Part of Julia?
All of them?
You're being watched.
Which one?
I can't give you a hint.
Looks?
Personality?
I see.
Looks?
Which one?
I can't give you a hint.
I see.
The first one?
The first one is the part, right?
Yes.
The first one is the part?
The first one?
Let's go!
I like this one.
I think so, too.
If you're wrong, you'll be punished.
It'll be funny if Julia is wrong.
Let's open it!
All of them?
All of them.
Eyes, face.
Let's start!
Do you have any?
What is your favorite part of Julia?
My favorite part of Julia is...
Everything.
You're right!
That's not fair!
You said you like everything.
I like everything.
You did it!
Kana-Yu, Julia, Hitoka, and Aki!
Hitoka and Aki are correct!
We're on the same team!
I don't think it's fair.
If you were to choose, who would you
choose?
I'd choose Egao.
I'd choose all of them.
You look like you're laughing.
The three of them are correct!
Everything is focused on theshaped.
2 more!
What do you want to do someday?
What do I want to do?
I didn't think about that.
What do you want to do?
What do I want to do?
This is a bit difficult.
I think everyone wants to do it at
least once.
You've never done it, right?
No, I haven't.
I know!
I know someone who has done it alone.
Who?
Someone who has done it alone.
I know who.
Yes, I have.
What?
There are many.
Yes, there are.
Please check the description for the
translation!
Wait, wait.
What's this?
Looks?
Hiyori-chan has never done it.
Why?
What did Hiyori do?
I don't know.
Hiyori-chan has never done it.
Why haven't we all done it?
Isn't it because it's rare?
What did Hiyori do?
What?
I don't know.
You want to try, right?
I definitely want to try.
Okay, everyone, open!
Gunpla defence
What's the first thing you want to do
on the river?
I want to play in the river!
That's cute!
I've never heard of it!
You want to play in the river?
I'll go next!
Go ahead!
What do you want to try someday?
I want to try someday!
What?
I want to try someday.
You're looking at the question.
Oh, I see.
Yes, what I want to try someday is...
Wakko Sawa!
Do you know what it is? I don't think
you know.
I've never said Wakko Sawa in my life.
I don't care if it's not once. I want
to try Wakko Sawa.
I think so, too.
Oh, it's Wakko Sawa.
It's not.
Kawagoe.
Yes, I ate it with Kawagoe.
It's not Wakko Sawa.
I'm like this, too.
But you said it.
I said it.
I think so.
But, you know, Oharu, you said you
wanted to do this.
Which one?
Ganmenpai.
Yes, it was Wakko Sawa.
It was difficult.
You didn't know that, did you?
I didn't know.
Then, the last one.
The current points are Kanamin and Jiki
Toka 3 points, Julia 2 points, Aki and
Hiyo 1 point.
I don't like it.
I think it's too difficult.
Please look forward to the next video!
I've never heard of it.
I'm kidding.
If you get the next question right,
you'll get 2 points.
If you get the last question right.
If you get the last question right,
you'll get 2 points.
The last question!
What animal do you want to be when
spring comes?
I also wrote multiple answers.
Anything is fine.
I don't think so.
I can't think of any names.
If I get one right, I'll give you a
point.
You can write a lot.
If I get one wrong, I'll get one wrong.
I can't write a lot.
Let's do it this way.
Let's open it together!
Ta-da!
Raw kimono!
Oh!
Oh no!
This is...
Do you see it?
Here you go!
What kind of animal do you want to be
when you are reborn?
I have a lot of animals I want to be
when I am reborn.
I think you all know what I mean.
I want to be a dog or a sloth.
If you don't know what I mean, please
look it up.
I want to be a monkey or a hyena.
I want to be a mandrill.
It would be great if you know what I
mean.
Everyone got it right!
I want everyone to see the mangrove.
I've seen it before!
I've seen it in the movie, but it's
called Lion King.
That's right!
I want to be a father to this!
Kanamin and Hitoka got the same score!
Yay!
So, Oharu is Kanamin and Hitoka!
So, the last one is Aki and Hiyori!
We are going to imitate animals!
nosotros
Como
ah ah ah
pa
I won't let go of your hand
I'm going to go from there.
From the entrance.
I can see it.
It's like a movie.
Thank you for watching.
What are you doing?
Are you in a relationship?
Are you a couple?
Do you talk to each other?
I don't know what we are talking about.
Ramen
Oh, yeah!
Tasty
This is a soup
Aki-chan
So
Salt
Miso
Came out at that time
Miso...
Shime...
I'm a little scared.
It's a big one.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Hello, I'm Mandrill.
I'm Mandrill. I'm from there.
Do you want to call your parents?
Yes, I do.
Kaho-chan!
We started YouTube.
Oh, really?
Yes.
I want you to appear because you are
cute.
Thank you.
Everyone, please subscribe to our
channel.
Please.
Hiyori, if you think I'm cute, I don't
feel uncomfortable, I look good, please
press the button.
Please subscribe to my channel and
leave a comment.
Thank you for watching my video.
Please like this video, subscribe to my
channel, and leave a comment.
I'm going to record this.
I'm not going to do it.
No, no, no.
I'm going to record this.
Thank you for your parts area
Waiting
Please subscribe to our channel and
follow us on Twitter!
I can say it now, the reason for my
tears
Is that I realized I was lost
I remember it right away
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, yesterday's me
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day
I play the sound of a rainbow
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, yesterday's me
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a flower
I cry and dance
I wear a rainbow dress